funwithmama.com 2019-12-15

# Disclosure and Privacy Policy - Fun with Mama

**_This policy was last updated on May 15, 2018_**

Your privacy is important to Fun With Mama. The policy below outlines how your personal information is collected and how it is used when you use our website.

You agree to the terms of this policy when you use this website. This privacy policy may change from time to time. If any changes are made, then you will be notified by revising the date at the top of this policy.

**About Fun With Mama**  
Founded in 2009 and based in the United States Of America, Fun With Mama is an independently operated blog run by Nadia. This website includes kids activity ideas, family travel, entertainment, craft tutorials, parenting and motherhood lifestyle, etc

**How Information is Collected**

Here is how your information is collected on Fun With Mama

  * if you subscribe to the newsletter
  * if you leave a comment on the blog
  * if you purchase a product via the Fun With Mama store
  * through website cookies and log files
  * through Google Analytics

**Newsletter**

If you decide to join the newsletter via any of the many sign up forms located throughout this website, then your first name and email address are required. We require your email address in order to send you the emails and we require your first name so that my emails to you will include a friendly personalized note. 

At the bottom of every email I send, you will find a link to unsubscribe. You may unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time. If you are having trouble unsubscribing or would like to be removed from the newsletter, then simply send me an email at nadia@funwithmama.com  asking to be removed.

I currently use ActiveCampaign as my email service provider ([read their privacy policy here](https://www.activecampaign.com/privacy-policy/) ). Your data is collected and then passed to them. Tags are used within ActiveCampaign to track your actions and page visits so that future emails can be better tailored to meet your needs.

Currently, I send a minimum of one to two emails per week. However, I will occasionally email you about products and other promotions that may be relevant to your interests. 

Free printables are sent directly to your email with a download link via a third party application called Leadpages ([read their privacy policy here](https://www.leadpages.net/privacy)).

Your email and name are never sold or given away to a third party.

All emails you receive are CAN-SPAM compliant. At the bottom of every email, you will find information on how to contact the sender, as well as information on how to unsubscribe.

**Blog Comments**

Love something you read on my blog? Then leaving a comment is a great way to do that! I personally love hearing your feedback. If you choose to leave a comment on a blog post, then please be aware that the comment is then public and visible to anyone who reads the comment section. Your email address is never shared or disclosed, but your name and comment will be visible to others.

It is highly recommended that you avoid leaving detailed personal information in your comments (like your last name.)

I reserve the right to remove comments deemed as inappropriate, threatening, profane, or spammy without notice.

**Store Purchases**

Products in the Fun With Mama store are sold via WooCommerce. Your name, email address, and country are required during the checkout process. This information is required in order to send you the purchased product and to determine whether or not the EU VAT tax should be applied to your purchase.

The details you enter are stored by the third party applications. All payments are made through PayPal, which does not store your financial information once the transaction has been processed.

I also sell products via affiliate programs. Each program collects and retains their own data. I do not have access to the personal information that is collected by these affiliate programs. It is best to read their individual privacy policies for more information on how your data is collected and used.

**Cookies**

Cookies store user-specific information into a log. I use the following cookies on Fun With Mama:

  * Amazon (for advertising)
  * Facebook Pixel (for Facebook ad targeting): [Read how the Pixel works](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/742478679120153?helpref=faq_content)
  * Google Analytics (for tracking website traffic and user behavior): [Read how their cookies work](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage)
  * Active Campaign (for email tracking): [Read how their site tracking works](https://help.activecampaign.com/hc/en-us/articles/221542267-An-overview-of-Site-Tracking)

**Google Analytics**

Fun With Mama uses Google Analytics to track website performance and user behavior. It provides information on pageviews, referral sources, and other valuable information that helps me adapt the content I write for this website. Google Analytics does capture anonymous data about location, age, gender, and interests, but I have no way to connect that information and specifically identify you. Google Analytics may also capture your IP address as you make your way around this website. User and event data is retained for 26 months and then is automatically deleted. You can [read more about that here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=en&utm_id=ad).

**Advertisements on Fun With Mama**

To support this website, third party advertisements are used. Fun With Mama currently runs advertisements via AdThriev. They may use cookies or web beacons when they advertise here on Fun With Mama

**Social Media Privacy**

Fun With Mama uses various social media platforms. Fun With Mama is not responsible for what you post on Fun With Mama’s social media channels.  

**Parental Consent**

If you are under 16 years old, you must first have parental permission before using our website or entering personal information in order to show you tailored ads to you.

**Final Notes on this Privacy Policy**

You have the right to access your personal data and know how it is being processed. Hopefully, the policy above adequately explains how your data is used.

Personal information will not be transferred unless we are legally obligated to do so. If you would like your information to be removed from our systems, please contact funwithmama@gmail.com. You can request to be removed at any time.

Fun With Mama contains links to other websites. As such, Fun With Mama is not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites or the third party applications it uses.

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at nadia@funwithmama.com

The privacy of visitors to Fun With Mama is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit funwithmama.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We use third party advertisements on funwithmama.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Fun With Mama respects your privacy and values each and every reader. I don’t publicize any of your information and only track information to collect data through cookies. This gives me a better idea about which pages are doing well on the blog, how you found me, what people are currently interested in and more.

Fun With Mama accepts sponsorships, paid advertisements and other forms of compensation.

**Sponsored posts:  **A sponsored post is a blog post written in exchange of compensation for writing about a product. However, all opinions and thoughts are true and honest. This compensation may influence the content of posts but never my honest opinion. I will only recommend products that I have tried, tested and used myself (unless otherwise noted). These posts will be clearly noted.

The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely mine and my children’s experiences. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

What this all means is that I will only recommend products that I believe are wonderful and I will give you my fair evaluation.

**Amazon Affiliates:  **We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. This program provides blogs like myself with compensation for advertising for Amazon.com and for linking to Amazon.com products when appropriate in a post. Having an Amazon.com link in a post does not influence my feelings on that product and all opinions stated remain my own.  Amazon, as a third party, also uses cookies to track their advertising on my site and their links. You are welcome to read more about the Amazon Affiliates program in their [Operating Agreement](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/gp/associates/agreement?ie=UTF8&pf_rd_i=assoc_join_menu&pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&pf_rd_p=&pf_rd_r=&pf_rd_s=assoc-right-1&pf_rd_t=501&ref_=amb_link_84018271_11&rw_useCurrentProtocol=1).

**Parental supervision: Please note that parental (or teacher) supervision is required for ALL activities posted on Fun With Mama.**

This disclosure policy is subject to change without notice. If you have any questions please e-mail me at nadia at funwithmama.com
